BGM
Oh, live!
I don't feel like opening it.
Mr. Tamura, please!
Hello everyone. I'm Honoo Tamura from Sakurazaka46.
Today I went to Osaka for the first pitch of JT Marvelous' home game!
Wow!
Funny people!
My hometown is Osaka.
I'm very happy to be able to come back like this after a long time!
By the way, I played volleyball from kindergarten to college!
Ta-da!
This girl's name is Marveline.
I had a chance to practice on the main court a little while ago.
I know it's hard to understand...
I was practicing with Kira yesterday during the Anilanori wave.
I was able to do some really amazing tricks...
Oh well...
Which way is it going to fly? My serve.
Oh, will it fly away?
A little more, a little more...
Let's go!
Oh, come on!
Wow, you're just in time.
I don't have the strength.
I don't know what to do.
No more.
Ah!
I can take it, right?
I'm going to go to the sub-arena after this to practice, so I don't know how my arms are going to be a little bit for the real thing, but I'll do my best. I will go to the sub-arena after this to practice, so I don't know how my arms will be for the real event, but I will do my best.
Good morning, I am Hama Tamura from SAKURA SAKAMOTO SIX. I am Tamura Hama of SAKURA SAKAMOTO SIX.
Good morning, I am Tamura Hama from SAKURA SAKAMOTO SIX.
Good morning.
Why do you sleep so much?
Don't you feel it's the first time?
The point is the toss.
If you get the toss right.
I'm sure you'll be fine.
Thank you very much.
That's totally high!
It's the same height as in high school.
Really?
You were hit at this height.
It wasn't like that.
I only did this much.
It's amazing what training can do.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
You found your pitch, lesson.
Wow!
I'm going to go throw out the first pitch now.
I'm really nervous, but...
I've managed to ask God for help, so...
I hope I'll be successful.
I'll do my best
I'll be there.
I'll be waiting for you.
I'll be waiting for you. We'll be waiting for you.
I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't.
Don't worry, we'll do our best.
Oh, I'm going to die, I'm going to die!
Today, Ms. Yasuno Tamura of Sakurazaka Defense came to support JT Barberas!
Before the game begins, please welcome Ms. Tamura and throw out the first pitch.
Please give a big round of applause!
Hello everyone, I'm Yasuno Tamura of Sakurazaka 46.
Thank you for allowing me to throw out the first pitch at JT Barberas' home game today.
I have been playing volleyball since I was a student, and I am very happy to be able to come back to my hometown Osaka in this way.
I'm looking forward to the game today, and I'm looking forward to working with you.
Thank you very much, Mr. Tamura.
Now I would like to move on to the first pitch.
You've been playing volleyball since you were a little girl, all the way through college.
Well, I came in two hours early to practice.
Actually, I was secretly watching.
Let's see if she's going to make a great serve.
Mr. Tamura, please.
Nice.
2023-24VLG Devision Farm Woman JT Marvelous Burgers
Thank you very much.
We're done.
I didn't really know what was going on anymore.
I was so nervous the whole time.
But all the players were really nice to me the whole time I was talking.
I didn't know what I was saying.
I didn't know what I was saying, but they were smiling and listening to me. He was smiling and listening to me.
That's all I really needed to do today!
I got it, but I didn't know if I hit it or not.
But I couldn't think about whether I mitted the ball or not, or what my form was like.
I was so nervous that I couldn't think about it.
I'm going to check the video later.
I'm so nervous, I'm going to watch the game now.
Yay, bye-bye!
Thank you for your hard work!
The game is over.
I was under a little bit of pressure.
I heard you won 8 games in a row.
Congratulations!
I will continue to support them.
Channel and Sakurazaka Channel
I have a difficult voice!
Please subscribe to my channel, click the "Good" button and leave a comment!
I'll be waiting for you.
See you soon!
Bye bye!
I'm going back to Tokyo.
I'm leaking.